丁度·巴拉斯电影作品
《奸情》
领衔主演:安娜.金斯卡娅
里卡多·马里诺
马克斯·帕洛蒂
内拉·露西斯
亲我 达里奥 求你了！
Kiss me Dario, please!
亲我的脖子
Kiss me on the neck.
就像你初次吻我…
Like you used to...
欲望高涨 激情四射地亲我
just one kiss, but sensual, passionate.
8月26日
August 26th.
我自己也不知道为什么深夜1点写下这些东西
I don't know why I'm writing this at one in the morning.
我只知道如果不写出来, 我就会歇斯底里尖叫
I only know that if I don't, I'll scream.
达里奥是个好丈夫 我也深爱着他
Dario is a wonderful husband and I love him,
但是自从结婚以后, 与他云雨我就再难达到高潮
but since we've been married I can't reach orgasm with him.
为什么？究竟哪里错了？
Why? What's wrong?
我们结婚不过半年
It's only been six months since our wedding.
那事儿似乎每况愈下, 日复一日 单调乏味
and things seem to get more boring, flavourless and banal every day.
往日的激情 惊喜 欢乐与狂野
What happened to all the enthusiasm, surprise, fun.
都跑到哪儿去了？
and craziness we had before?
让我抓住 会给你们好看！
If I catch you, you're dead!
让我来收拾你 你个小骚货！
I'll fix you, you naughty girl!
哦 爽…爽…达里奥 舔我！我的小妹妹欲火高涨啊
Oh yes...yes... Dario, lick me! My pussy's on fire.
萨堤尔(色狼)眼前的歧途…是选择信徒通往俄摩拉城(罪恶之都)的路…
The satyr's crossroads...the Apostles' road to Gomorrah...
还是直达所多码(罪恶之地)的污渎小道？
or the unhallowed alleyway to Sodom?
哦 不！肉棒不能进！除非我们已经是夫妻
Oh no! Not this! Only when we're husband and wife.
哦 好爽！肏得小妹妹好爽！
Oh yes! Give it to me!
这辈子从未这样爽过！
I've never come so much in my life!
昨天文学节上 有人把它硬塞给我
They foisted it on me at the Literature Festival yesterday.
你帮我看看 我相信你的眼光, 达里奥留言
Why not take a look at it? You know I trust your judgement. Dario.
附言：你睡得正香，我不想叫醒你！
PS: You were sleeping so peacefully I didn't want to wake you up!
我还没反应过来，就被他压在身下
"I found myself pressed against him without realising it.
我俩双唇紧贴 他的舌头贪婪地在我嘴里搅动
His mouth glued onto mine, his tongue scavenging greedily,
甚至想直捣我炙热的喉咙
pushing itself into my parched throat.
我无法呼吸，却又无法抗拒
I couldn't breathe, but I didn't break away.
我的胸脯感觉到他肌肉的起伏, 充斥着我呼吸的 尽是他的气味
I felt his muscles rippling against my breasts. I breathed in his smell.
我充耳所闻 尽是那些舞者的呻吟
The groans of the dancers filled my ears
有人对我低语说我是个婊子
and someone whispered that I was a whore.
但这一切 似乎对我都已无关紧要
But it all seemed so insignificant to me.
我的全部注意力集中在
The stranger's hand under my skirt
陌生的手伸进我的裙下 放在臀间
and on my ass was all that I cared about.
那对笨拙而又强壮的手掌拉着我, 让我紧贴他的腹部
Those strong, blundering hands that pressed me to his stomach
逼着我用身体摩擦他那话儿
and compelled me to rub myself against his cock,
那玩意儿好生粗大 膨胀得像要夺裤而出
which seemed ready to burst out of his trousers.
还是那双手 突破我亵裤的防线
Those same hands that invaded my panties
我的仙人洞可怜地落入它的掌握
and grabbed my pussy.
在我花瓣间翻江倒海的那只巧手仿佛发出阵阵箭簇
His finger shot between my cunt lips like an arrow.
我的花径湿得一片狼籍 蓬门顺从地洞开, 他没有遭遇任何抵抗
I was moist, open, yielding, he didn't meet any resistance.
直到现在我还感觉到他笨拙的手指在我的屄里抽插
I can still feel it now, his clumsy finger on my pussy
一股冷颤直冲脊背 依旧令我回味无穷
and the cold shiver that ran down my spine.
我三下五除二 解除他的裤子
I undid his trousers
踢掉我的鞋子
and kicked off my shoes.
我呼吸短促 屄缝溢满甜蜜的汁液
My breath was short and my pussy was wet.
我肆无忌惮 毫无羞耻
I felt free to show my eagerness
展示我膨胀的欲望
and my desire without shame."
在这儿呢
Here it is.
这书让你昏昏欲睡？我不会怪罪你睡觉
The book made you nod off? I don't blame you for sleeping.
这次文学节简直无聊透顶！
The Literature Festival is a total drag!
你要不就去德泰宫观赏景致？
Why don't you visit Palazzo Te?
你好放肆！
How dare you!
你干什么？放开我！
What are you doing? Leave me alone!
你喜欢这些壁画 嗯？
You like the frescoes, huh?
瞧他俩在干啥？
Do you see those two?
孩子们 集中精力看壁画！
Kids? Look at the frescoes!
我们是来这儿研究朱利奥·罗曼诺的, 用心点！
We're here to study Giulio Romano, pay attention.
他真可爱！
He is cute though!
多可爱的奶头！
Those lovely little tits!
迷人的小屄！
That lovely little pussy!
快点 我们要迟到了！
Hurry up, we're late!
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
有件事想跟你说说…
I've got to tell you something...
怎么 把我的信用卡刷爆了？
You've gone over the limit on my credit card?
那个…我…
Well...I...
你还好吧？我当然不忙
Hello? Of course I'm not busy!
我该怎么开口？
How can tell him?
难道照直说亲爱的 今天我做了对你不忠的事
Today I cheated on you, my love.
老公 我给你戴绿帽了！
Darling, I've been unfaithful!
达里奥…我私通野汉
Dario...I'm an adulteress.
你刚才说什么？
Well? You were saying?
我想跟你说…
I wanted to tell you...
我们非得出席这个宴会吗？
Do we really have to go to this party?
这可是开幕盛典 难道你想要他们炒我的鱿鱼？
It's the grand opening, do you want them to fire me?
届时宾客济济 其中有著名作家, 你会有乐趣的
There'll be lots of guests, famous writers, you'll have fun.
好无聊啊！
What a drag!
就像你们东北那边说的 “生意终归是生意”
As you say in the North-East, "Business is business."
乖啊 别磨磨蹭蹭
Come on, hurry up.
我今天差点被人强奸了！
I was nearly raped today!
我说 我这娇艳迷人的玉门关…
I said this lovely little pussy
被人硬捅进去了 好比鸟儿被穿在烤肉叉上
was speared like a bird on a skewer.
你听见没有 老公！
Did you hear, darling?
我说我被人强奸了！
I said that I was raped!
我晓得啦！
I understood!
差点还是既成事实？
Nearly or actually?
你不相信我的话？
You don't believe me?
我当然信 宝贝. 谁干的好事？那个酒店的摩洛哥侍应？
Of course I do, darling. Who by? That Moroccan waiter in the hotel?
不 是个陌生人
No, by a stranger.
就在德泰宫
At Palazzo Te.
这是被老公疏忽的老婆做的白日梦吧？
The fantasies of a neglected wife?
你听着 我甚至还觉得很爽
Look, I even enjoyed it!
哦 是吗？
Oh, really?
既然你这么玩世不恭, 今天的派对干脆别穿内裤出席
Seeing as you're so outrageous, don't wear any panties to the party.
你当我不敢么！
You say it as if I wouldn't be capable!
快点 你要累我迟到了！
Come on, you'll make me late!
滚你妈的！
Fuck off!
我想让一个情人站在另一个情人面前说
I'd like to place one lover in front of the other and say:
这是当代趋势吗？
is this the current trend?
心灵再也不能承受重负
The heart can no longer shoot its load.
臀部是伟大的平等主义者
The ass is a great leveller.
阴户是心灵的眼睛！
The pussy is the minds eye.
粗鄙不堪！
How vulgar!
一点也不！能指是真正的标志！
Not at all! The signifier is the real signified!
注:一种语言学理论,语言有两个组成部分:所指和能指;
所指即文字能指即此文字对应的符号或概念
如此说来 “情欲”去除所有文化价值后就成了“色情”
Eroticism loses all cultural value that way, it becomes pornography.
大师 是否“色情”就是“情欲”?
Is it true, maestro, that pornography is to eroticism
“吹箫”其实就是“口淫”？
what the blow job is to fellatio?
诚然如此 这只是语义学和语言学的问题
Exactly, it's just a matter of semantics and language.
简单点说 就是舌头的活儿！
Of tongues, if anything!
艺术成为色情 或者说反之亦然？
Does art become pornography or vice versa?
你的出版社能赚个盆满钵盈 还正是靠了性
Sex is the only thing that keeps your publishing houses a float.
还有《圣经》 那从来都是最畅销的书
And the Bible, it's always the number one seller.
宗教 性 暴力, 这些就是成功的秘诀 为此干杯！
Religion, sex, excess, a recipe for success! Cheers!
住手！
Stop it!
会被人家看见的
They can see us.
《青楼情史》一个月就卖了20万本！
"Whores in Love". 200,000 copies in a month!
-这位是…？ -麦克斯·扎诺克
- Who? - Max Zanouk.
最有前途的作家之一
One of our most promising authors.
恭喜你了
Ah, congratulations.
你会料到在这儿见着我么…
You expected to see me here...
-求求你 别在这儿 -你居然是真空上阵！
- Please, not here. - You've got no panties on!
那又如何 不过是在跟我丈夫斗气
So what, it's just to spite my husband.
-这里水漫金山也是由于赌气吗？ -别碰我
- Is that why you're all wet too? - Leave me alone.
那是因为我酒喝多了
It's all the wine I've drunk.
我早就想找你了
I've looking for you.
你在听吗?
Are you listening.
-玛尔塔·贝托鲁奇 -西维娅
- Marta Bortoluzzi - Silvia
再次见到你可真高兴！
How nice to see you again!
-文学节期间你一直在吗？ -是的 直到周日
- Staying for the whole festival? - Yes, till Sunday.
太好了！
Wonderful!
-达里奥呢？ -他也来了
- And Dario? - He's here too.
你丈夫呢？
And your husband?
亨利不幸得留守巴黎…
Unfortunately Henry's had to stay in Paris...
你也知道…出版社这块…
You know how it is... work, the publishing house.
我是和弗朗索瓦一起来的
I'm here with François,
-亨利的秘书 你还记得他吗？ -当然记得
- His secretary. Remember him? - Of course.
你婚礼那天他也去了托尔切洛
He was at Torcello the day you got married.
不过…我们似乎来得不是时候？
But...did we interrupt something?
哪里的话 我正要上洗手间
No, not at all. I'm on my way to the bathroom.
-陪我去吗？ -好啊
- Will you come with me? - I'd love to!
我有好多话想跟你聊呢
We've got so much to talk about.
恭喜你啦！
Congratulations!
-什么时候学会不穿内裤外出的？ -不是你想的那回事儿
- When did you start going without? - It's not what you think.
-真的吗？ -真的！
- Oh, no? - No!
-都怪达里奥 -你懂得这么玩 真难得！
- It's Dario's fault. - You're lucky you play those games!
跟你说了 不是那回事儿
I told you, it's not like that.
其实 我和他之间不太协调
In fact, things aren't going too well between us.
-你是指床上那回事儿？ -我跟他云雨不出高潮来了
- You mean in bed? - I can't orgasm with him anymore.
这很正常呀 甜心！
But that's normal, darling!
每个人迟早都会那样
It happens to everyone sooner or later!
-我也一样 -那你怎么办？
- It happened to me too. - And what did you do?
你以为我为啥会跟弗朗索瓦来文学节？
Why do you think I came to the festival with François?
他可不光是亨利的秘书
He's not just Henry's secretary,
那方面才是妙用无穷！
he's an incredible stud!
你对丈夫不忠就没有罪恶感？
You feel guilty for cheating on your husband?
罪恶感归罪恶感 可我就是觉得爽极了
There's guilt and guilt. I feel really good.
事实上 出轨之后我跟亨利之间还更有进步
In fact, so good that things have even improved with Henry.
-哪方面？ -各个方面 甚至床上
- In what way? - Every way. Even in bed.
亲爱的玛蒂娜 嫉妒是疗效最佳的春药
Jealousy, my dear Martina, is the strongest aphrodisiac.
没有什么东西比猜忌…
There's nothing better than suspicion
更能重新点燃伴侣对你的欲望 相信我！
to rekindle your partner's desire, believe me!
找个可以肏得你爽翻天的男人
Find someone who'll give you a good fucking.
对达里奥来说 没有比这更好的礼物了
You couldn't give Dario a better present.
就比如…刚才那个陪着你的男人
Someone...like that man you were with, for example.
可我只是今晚才认识他的, 甚至都不知道他叫什么！
But I only met him this evening, I don't even know his name!
有时候 名字和时间长短并不重要
Sometimes you don't need names or a long time.
看长短要看另一方面…
You need something else that's long...
可是…背着达里奥跟别的男人偷情…
But... to be unfaithful to Dario, screw with someone else...
-我都无法确认自己能否做到 -你能的 甜心
- I don't know if I could. - You could, darling.
你肯定行 不是说所有男人都对你“见花泄”
You could. The notorious "quick one"!
不过你得有分寸
You've just got to do it right.
-啥意思？ -要分清主次
- Meaning? - Get your priorities right.
-什么主次？ -要合情合理
- What priorities? - The legitimate ones.
我从来只让弗朗索瓦走后门
I only let François use the rear entrance.
至于前面嘛 却是时刻留给亨利享用的
The front one is reserved for Henry.
你可真是个荡妇！
You're such a slut!
恭喜 小姐们, 屁股可不光是用来排泄的
Congratulations, ma'am. The ass isn't just for making poo-poo.
正如男人们在我那里面说的, 绰绰有余！
And as they say in my neck of the woods, it hasn't got a meter!
这双高跟鞋好伤我的脚
These heels have ruined my feet!
可是…
But...
-怎么了？ -你的内裤呢？
- What is it? - Your panties?
-我没穿 -我看得见 那你的内裤哪去了？
- I'm not wearing any. - l can see, where are they?
-我之前根本就没穿  -什么意思？
- I didn't put any on. - What do you mean?
你不记得啦？是你赌我敢不敢不穿的
You were the one who dared me to, remember?
你敢归敢啊 要是被人察觉怎么办？
There are dares and dares. What if someone had noticed?
要是我告诉你当真有人发现了呢？
What if I tell you they did?
-你这么说是什么意思？ -跳舞时总有些手不太规矩
- What do you mean by that? - Hands can wander during a dance.
就一件薄薄的丝裙 有什么摸不出来
You can feel everything through a silk dress!
是那个跟你跳舞的狗杂种？
That son of a bitch who danced with you!
-你认识他？ -我才不会跟这种人扯上关系！
- You know him? - I don't mix with people like that!
那你干嘛怒气冲天？
Why get so hot under the collar then?
这种鸟人只要看看脸谱 就知道是龟公 舞男…
You can see in his face that he's a whoremonger, a gigolo
肮脏的变态！
and a filthy pervert!
难怪说男人不坏 女人不爱
That must be why women find him attractive.
你可别说喜欢上他了！
Don't say you like him!
我也是个女人 对不对？
Well, I'm a woman too, aren't I?
-可你首先是我妻子 -是么！
- First of all, you're my wife. - You don't say!
我差点忘了
I'd forgotten.
那种男人只会对婊子感兴趣
Men like that are only interested in whores.
从他揉捏我的方式看 我肯定也是婊子了
From the way he was squeezing me, I must be a whore too.
你今晚究竟怎么了？
Anyway, what's got into you this evening?
没什么 我不过是想告诉你发生了什么
Nothing, I just wanted to tell you what happened.
我看你朝着他笑 当时就想警告你
l saw you smile at him and l wanted to warn you.
你看到我笑了？那你还看到点别的没有？
You saw me smile? Well then, you didn't see anything.
难不成我还应该看到点什么？
What else should I have seen?
比方说 他摸了我的屁股
He touched my ass, for example.
-你是不是有点过分了？ -我？
- Aren't you going too far? - Me?
是他过分才对 他把手伸到我裙子底下
He went too far, he put his hand under my skirt.
-他发现你没穿内裤？ -他还摸了我的屄
- He found out you had no panties? - He touched my pussy.
-那你干什么了？ -我让他伸进两根手指
- What did you do? - I let him stick two fingers in.
-你当时肯定春水泛滥了 -简直堪比威尼斯水城涨潮
- I'm sure you were all wet. - Like Venice at high tide.
-他胀起来没有？ -堪比铁棍！
- Did he get a hard on? - And how!
-比你硬多了！ -你俩入港没有？
- Stiffer than yours! - Did you fuck?
别紧张 你不是觉得这样太过分了？
Take it easy, don't you think that's going too far?
玛尔塔 你都让我快疯了
Oh, Marta, you drive me crazy.
-等等 我们就在这儿干 -站着搞？畜生才会这样
- Wait, let's do it here. - Standing up? That's for animals.
-这有什么？ -床上比这舒服多了
- What's wrong with that? - The bed's more comfortable.
过来 我忍不住了
Come on, I'm desperate.
谁啊？
Who is it?
贝托鲁奇太太 您有信
A message, Mrs Bortoluzzi.
稍等！
Just a moment!
-对不起 我没零钱 -没关系 太太
- Sorry, I don't have any change. - That's all right, ma'am.
12点钟 “猪船”上见.  附注：当然别穿内裤！-莱昂
12 o'clock at "The Pig's Boat",  PS: No panties, of course! Leon.
神经病！不过…
What a nerve! But...
莱昂…好听的名字！
Leon... nice name!
都11点了！
It's eleven!
我今天整日都会呆在外国文学馆
I'll be in the Foreign Literature Pavilion all day.
你要是觉得无聊就过来找我 , 我爱你.. 达里奥
If you get bored, why not drop in? I love you, Dario.
附注：这回记得穿好内裤！
PS: Wear some panties this time!
我该如何是好？
What should I do?
去“猪船”还是外国文学馆？
"The Pig's Boat" or foreign literature?
找莱昂还是达里奥？
Leon or Dario?
穿还是不穿内裤？
Panties or no panties?
做选择题最讨厌！
It's a drag having to choose!
您早！
Good morning!
找人吗？
Looking for someone?
嗯…是的
Well... yes.
我找一位法国人 莱昂先生
A French gentleman, Monsieur Leon.
-他应该订过席位 -好的 女士 这边请
- He should have a booking. - Of course, ma'am. This way.
-要不要边等边喝点什么？ -不了 谢谢
- A drink while you're waiting? - No, thanks.
您随便
As you wish.
忘掉普奇尼 罗西尼和贝利尼！
Forget Puccini, Rossini and Bellini!
威尔第 只有威尔第 永远的威尔第！
Verdi, only Verdi. Verdi forever!
可是和《塞维尔的理发师》根本没法比…
But there's no comparison with "The Barber..."!
算了 我还是来杯马提尼酒
I've changed my mind. A Martini.
-苦艾酒要红还是要白？ -红吧
- Vermouth? White or red? - Red.
马上就来 女士
Right away, ma'am.
再来一杯！
Another one!
-还要红的？ -白的！
- Red? - White!
你崇拜的罗西尼何时写出过这样的…
When did your Rossini ever write anything like...
侍应 买单！
Waiter, the bill!
再来一杯！红酒
Another one! Red.
谢谢
Thank you!
-想让我独自一人进餐吗？ -王八蛋！你足足迟到1个小时
- Want me to eat alone? - Bastard! You're an hour late.
要怪就怪…
Blame it on...
满脑子臭屁又没胆量鸡蛋里挑骨头的家伙！
Cowardly nitpickers with farting brains!
除非你有问必答 否则我可不原谅你
I'll only excuse you if you tell me something.
你怎么晓得我住哪家酒店？
How did you know which hotel I'm staying at?
经纪人都住那家
Managers always go to that one.
那么好色淫乱 脾气糟糕的法国佬又住哪家呢？
Where do horny, bad mannered Frenchmen go?
就住在经纪人太太们的两腿之间
Between the legs of the managers wives.
打扰一下…
Excuse me...
填馅意大利面条 还有烤鸭 两份
Stuffed pasta and roast duck for two.
要不要来点蔬菜？
And some vegetables?
我们上洗手间吧
Let's go to the bathroom.
-厕所？ -那边
- The toilet? - Through there.
抱歉！马提尼喝多了…
Excuse me! The Martini...
我的报告…
My report...
放他妈哪儿了？
Where the fuck is it?
7月20日 我们结婚四个月后渐渐起了些变化
July 20th, we've been married four months. Something's changed.
达里奥不再那么在意我
Dario is less attentive towards me
而且他肏起我来不再像以前那样激情澎湃
and he doesn't fuck me like he used to.
8月13日
August 13th.
达里奥根本不晓得我在写日记
Dario doesn't know about this diary.
就算在他鼻子底下写 他也毫无觉察
It's quite easy to write in it right under his nose.
说不定我随便跟哪个上了床 他也会这样懵懵懂懂
Maybe it's just as easy to go to bed with other men.
8月26日
August 26th.
我自己也不知道, 为什么深夜1点写下这些东西
I don't know why I'm writing this at one in the morning.
我只知道如果不写出来 我就会歇斯底里尖叫
I only know that if I don't, I'll scream.
达里奥是个好丈夫 我也深爱着他
Dario is a wonderful husband and I love him.
但是自从结婚以后, 与他云雨我就再难达到高潮
But since we've been married, I can't reach orgasm with him.
为什么？究竟哪里错了？
Why? What's wrong?
我们结婚不过半年
It's only been six months since our weddings
那事儿似乎每况愈下
and things seem to get more boring, flavourless and banal
日复一日 单调乏味
every day.
往日的激情 惊喜 欢乐与狂野
What happened to all the enthusiasm, surprise, fun
都跑到哪儿去了？
and craziness we had before?
8月27日
August 27th.
差点被达里奥当场抓到我手淫
Dario almost caught me masturbating.
我听到他开门进来 就赶紧装睡
I pretended to be asleep when I heard him come in.
他看见我玉体横陈 有备而睡
He saw me naked and ready on the bed
却连碰都不碰我 他对我已经没有激情了？
but he didn't even touch me. Has he gone off me?
不 我知道他还爱着我 可他就是不来攻占娘子关
No, I know that he loves me, but he doesn't screw me.
就算他来肏了 我反倒觉得不如不肏！
And when he does I'd prefer it if he didn't!
8月28日 我得好好理清头绪
August 28th. I've got to get my head in order.
一定是德泰宫那些壁画的缘故 朱庇特(罗马保护神)的大鸡巴
It must be those frescoes at Palazzo Te, Jupiter's hard cock.
对 鸡巴 我说的是鸡巴！
Yes, cock. I said, cock!
说出来的感觉真好！鸡巴！鸡巴！鸡巴！
It's wonderful to say it! Cock! Cock!
真想在阳台上大声叫出来——鸡巴！
I want to shout it from the balcony. Cock!
假如让达里奥知道我都写了些什么 一定很好玩！
It'd be funny if Dario knew what I wrote in here!
我还差点让自己被一个陌生人干了屄
I almost allowed myself to be screwed by a stranger.
他一巴掌拍在我的屁股上
He slapped my ass
在我欣赏朱利欧·罗马诺的壁画时
while I was looking at Giulio Romano's frescoes.
要不是那群学生突如其来
If that group of students hadn't shown up,
我的屄说不定就让那陌生人肏了
I'd have let that stranger fuck me.
说来也巧 当晚的文学节宴会上 我又见到了他
As luck would have it, I saw him at the festival party.
他一把捉住我的手臂 把我拖进舞池
He grabbed me by the arm and dragged off to dance.
其实他是醉翁之意 我也一样！
He didn't care about dancing and neither did I!
他想找个隐蔽的角落
He wanted to find a secluded corner
好乘没有旁人和我丈夫看见 肏我的屄
where he could screw me without the others and my husband seeing.
就在达里奥的附近偷情 很够刺激！
What a turn on to do it with Dario nearby!
他没有给我喘息时间
He didn't give me time to catch my breath.
发现我没穿内裤 立即把手指插进我的水帘洞
He realised I had no panties on and slid a finger in my pussy.
当他按住我的头 把鸡巴凑到面前时 我也没有拒绝
I didn't resist when he pushed my head down onto his dick.
臭贱人！
Rotten slut!
原来她在浴室说的话不是幻觉！
So she wasn't just fantasising in the bathroom!
等我们回到酒店 达里奥也被燃起欲火
Dario had a hard on too when we got back to the hotel.
他有点奇怪 表现得很不安
He was weird, agitated.
就像他目睹了什么 还想进一步了解情况
It was as if he'd seen something and wanted to know more.
我听从了西维娅的建议
I followed Silvia's advice:
什么都别告诉他 表现得规规矩矩 但就是要让他疑神疑鬼
don't tell him everything, appear honest, but leave him in doubt.
8月30日
August 30th.
我终于知道他的名字了
I finally know his name.
真是命运的巧安排 他叫莱昂
By a quirk of fate, he's called Leon,
和达里奥给我看的书中男主人公的名字一样
like the man in the book that Dario gave me to read.
他本不该给我看那本书的
He shouldn't have given it to me.
玩火者必自焚
If you play with fire, you're going to get burned.
莱昂邀我到河边一条美食船上共进午餐
Leon invited me to lunch at an eatery by the river.
还要我不穿内裤！我本来就不想穿的
No panties! I wouldn't have worn them anyway.
我觉得自己有点不要脸 但和莱昂在一起 我什么都愿意做
I feel shameless, with Leon I'm willing to do anything.
尽管如此 我并不觉得有什么罪恶感 达里奥并没有失去我
Above all, I don't feel guilty, Dario's not losing out.
和莱昂在一起 不过像在品尝从未尝过的食物
With Leon it's like eating food I've never tasted before.
我一定要跟西维娅说说这事
I've got to tell Silvia about it,
我安排好跟她一起去阿巴诺(意大利温泉胜地)
I've arranged to go to Abano with her.
小心点 你这样会留下痕迹！
Careful, you'll leave a mark!
好爽
Hot
-你干嘛？ -留个印记啊
- What are you doing? - Leaving a mark.
不要 莱昂 不要
No...Leon...no!
巴隆 布特列 索林 你们在哪？哥伦布 夯歌 毕加索 还有你
Barron,Butlerov,Sorin, where are you? Colombo, Hangle, Picasso, and you...
宝贝 你的屁股夹得我好爽 别叫了…
Baby, you get me so hot ass clip. Hush...
你的屁股快让我爽死了！
I want to go crazy up your ass!
现在放松
Now relax.
一会我们拿些石子来做“石头疗法”
We'll be back later with some rocks for the "Stone Therapy".
[法语]滚蛋吧
-你真相信那种疗法吗？ -狗屁!
- Do you believe that therapy works? - Like fuck!
我相信鸡巴胜过相信石子
I believe in cocks not rocks!
要是这儿能有人让我们爽到潮吹可多好！
Imagine if there was someone here to get us nice and wet!
别说了 西维娅！我的面膜都要笑裂了
Cut it out, Silvia! You'll make me crack my mask!
来个半小时“比翼双飞式”(法语)舔阴
Half an hour of cunnilingus in the "poulet rôti"!
-什么式？ -“比翼双飞式”(法语)
- In the what? - Poulet rôti!
-我最喜欢的体位 -怎样的体位？
- My favourite position. - Which one is it?
就是这样…
This one...
像烤鸡！
The roast chicken!
-我懂了！ -我看你还是不懂
- I get it! - I don't think you do!
要真正弄懂 你最好亲自去试试
You have to try it to know what I mean.
要不就今晚 和达里奥…
Maybe tonight, with Dario...
算了吧 我和他之间还能有什么新意
You said it! There's nothing to try with him!
我还差点忘了！
I was forgetting!
那就和你宴会上认识的那位炮友试试啊
Well then, do it with your friend from the party.
-他叫莱昂是吗？ -你怎么知道？
- His name's Leon, isn't it? - How do you know?
刚才按摩师揉你屁股时 你喃喃自语说的
You said it while the masseuse was rubbing you.
当时在想他那双魔手了 是不是？
You were thinking about his hands, weren't you?
何止想他的手！
Not just his hands!
你们入过港了？
So you've done it!
我听从了你的建议
I followed your advice.
好样的 玛尔蒂娜！
Well done, Martina!
-感觉如何？ -你说的一点没错
- How did it go? - You were right.
我都好几个月没享受过这样的高潮了！
I'd not had an orgasm like that for months!
没错吧！
See!
快从实招来 有多详细说多详细
Come on, I want all the details.
我完全照你说的做 而且还很好地把握了分寸
I did exactly as you said, I got my priorities right.
太棒了！
Fantastic!
-他是不是对你感激流涕了？ -才怪！
- And did he appreciate it? - Did he ever!
-是他主动要走后门的 -这头贪婪的猪！
- He was the one who wanted it! - The greedy pig!
你们在哪入港的？
Where did it happen?
-他的鸡巴长什么样？ -你问那么清楚干嘛？
- What's his dick like? - Why all these questions?
你对他的兴趣未免过分点了吧？
Aren't you showing a bit too much interest in him?
有什么啊？毕竟…
Why not? After all...
我可是不介意玩玩3P的
I wouldn't mind a little threesome.
你…他…
You, him...
还有我…
and me...
我可是很有天分的
I'm very talented, you know.
肯定比刚才那按摩师还厉害
Even better than your masseuse.
这我不怀疑 不过…
I don't doubt it, but...
假如你想的话 我甚至可以叫上弗朗索瓦
I'll bring François along if you want.
他的舌功可是一流
He's great with his tongue.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
擅自剥脱面膜吗？
Taking your masks off by yourselves?
躺下！
Lie down!
西维娅的面膜很利索地脱落了下来！
Well, Silvia's mask had definitely been stripped off!
可跟她交谈一点帮助都没有
But talking to her hadn't done much good.
她满脑子想的就只有性 比我还差劲
All she thinks about is sex. She's worse than me.
我 她和莱昂玩3P…去她的！
Me, her and Leon... like hell!
要是莱昂更喜欢她怎么得了？
What if he prefers her over me?
我怎么了？在嫉妒么？莫非我堕入爱河了？
What's happening, am I jealous? Am I falling in love?
难道他不只是个让我愉悦的性工具？
Isn't he just supposed to be a stud to service me?
天 我现在可真是乱成一团麻！
Oh dear, I've got myself into a real mess!
嗨 甜心 今天怎么回来这么早？
Hi darling, how come you're back so soon?
-你在给谁写信？ -没有啊
- Who are you writing to? - No one.
不过是在记录些流水帐
I'm making out a list of things to do.
-比方说？ -就一些傻事
- Like? - Just silly things.
去参观维吉尔(古罗马诗人)的陵墓
Visiting Virgil's mausoleum,
去诺瓦拉利博物馆看曼特尼亚的壁画
going to the Nuvolari museum, seeing Mantegna's frescoes.
那你不打算跟我去文学节？
So you're not thinking of coming to the festival?
你知道我会很没趣的！
You know it bores me!
-你今天都做了些什么？ -出去走动了一下
- What did you do today? - I was out and about.
去哪儿？
Where?
去了阿巴诺
I went to Abano.
-去干什么？ -你问这个干嘛？
- What for? - Why do you ask?
问你问题 你就给我老实作答 臭婆娘！
I asked you a question, answer me, bitch!
-去做泥浴… -跟谁？
- A mud-bath treatment... - Who with?
西维娅
Silvia.
你要防着她点！还跟谁在一起？
Be careful of her! Who else went with you?
没了 就我俩
No one, it was just us two.
我们先在蒙塔格纳纳吃午饭 然后就去了阿巴诺
We had lunch in Montagnana and then we went to Abano.
当然了
Sure.
哪家餐厅吃的？
What was the restaurant called?
或者只是个小饭店？食物可口吗？
Or was it an eatery? Was the food good?
我记不得了 我们就匆匆吃了份快餐
I can't remember, we just had a quick snack!
那之前呢？
And before?
-什么之前？ -今天早上
- Before what? - Before, this morning.
你去见西维娅之前都干了些什么
What did you do before meeting Silvia?
没干什么
Nothing.
就睡觉 醒来后冲了个淋浴
I slept, took a shower.
好老套的谎言！
The usual lies!
-你怎么这样说？ -因为我了解你
- Why do you say that? - Because I know you.
-你不相信我？ -是
- Don't you believe me? - No.
我今天回过酒店来拿份报告 可你当时不在
I came back here for my report and you were out.
-可能我当时正在淋浴  -去你娘的！
- l must have been in the shower. - Like fuck you were!
-我只不过想幽默一下  -可是这并不好笑！
- It was a joke.  - It wasn't funny!
-我又不是故意这样  -难道不是吗？
- That wasn't what I intended.  - It wasn't?
那你的目的是什么？被人干 或许？
What was your intention? To get fucked, perhaps?
你有病吗？怎么能这样说话？
Are you mad? How can you say that?
文学节把你冲昏头了是不是？你到底想怎样？
This festival's gone to your head, what the hell do you want?
我就想知道你今天被谁肏了！
To know who screwed you today!
就冲你肏我那德性 我早就该找个替用！
The way you screw I should have got someone else!
骚货！
Slut!
王八！
Cuckold!
贱人！
Slut!
荡妇…她是淫娃荡妇！
Slut... she's a slut!
肮脏的贱货！
Filthy slut!
臭婊子！你就是个贱货！给我滚下车！
Dirty whore! You're just a slut! Get out of the car!
-我做错什么了？ -别让我再见到你 臭婊子！
- What did I do? - Get out of my sight, you bitch!
不 达里奥 求求你
No, Dario, please.
你这贱人就属于这里 就去马路上做街鸡吧！
That's were you belong, you cow! Whoring around in the road!
达里奥！
Dario!
西维娅！
Silvia!
西维娅！莱昂！
Silvia! Leon!
你们在干什么？
What are you doing?
今晚文学节有个闭幕晚宴
There's a party to close the festival tonight.
我希望你能来 昨天的事我很抱歉
I'd like you to be there. I'm sorry about yesterday.
假如之前对你有所疏忽 我保证以后不会再这样--达里奥手笔
And if I've been neglecting you, it won't happen again.
他读过吗？
Did he read it?
曼图亚酒店 莱昂
HOTEL MANTOVA Leon
喂 我是玛尔塔 我想和你见见
It's Marta, I've got to see you.
(你之前怎么不给我电话？)
Why didn't you call me before?
-我没机会 我要和你谈谈  -(说吧)
- I couldn't. I need to talk to you.  - Talk.
-不是电话里讲 要当面谈  -(你现在在哪？)
- Not like this, face to face.  - Where are you?
在酒店
In the hotel.
(想像我跟你在一起 你穿着衣服吗？)
Pretend I'm there with you. Are you dressed?
-穿着睡衣 怎么了？  -(睡衣下面呢？)
- I'm in my negligee, why?  - And underneath?
赤身裸体
I'm naked.
(抚摸自己 轻轻捏自己的乳头 想象是我的双手在你身上游走)
Touch yourself. Squeeze your tits, imagine my hands on your body.
莱昂 拜托！
Leon, please!
(还记得我鸡巴的味道吗？ 想象它就在你的喉管进出)
Remember how my cock tastes? Imagine it in your throat.
光靠想象不够 我要你真枪实弹
Imagining is not enough, I want you in the flesh.
-(就像在洗手间那样？) -就像在洗手间
- Like in the toilet? - Like in the toilet.
莱昂
Leon
你还在吗？我得见你 说真的
- Are you there? I've got to see you, it's serious.
(我在)
I'm here.
-(不过我要两点以后才有时间)  -没问题 在哪见面？
- Not before two though.  - That's fine, where?
(波利特街308号“里格莱托膳宿公寓”)
"Pension Rigoletto", 308, Via delle Bollette.
好吧 到时见
Okay, see you later.
我不需要这些
Well, I won't need them.
别抽什么大麻了！赶快把你的大家伙掏出来！
Forget that little joint! Get the big one out!
我迫不急待地想见莱昂 就提早离开酒店
I was so eager to see Leon  that I left the hotel early.
我就像发情的猫咪 不停地想找点东西来摩擦阴户
I was like a cat in heat that wanted  to rub against something.
我穿上件性感惹火的衣裳
I put on a sexy, provocative dress.
我强烈而又果断地相信自己 感受着命运由我一手操纵
I felt strong, decisive, sure of myself and mistress of my destiny.
我开始飘飘欲仙
My senses were heightened.
或许他们会以为我是瘾君子
Maybe they thought I was a drug addict.
这么想也不算离谱
They weren't far off the mark.
不过让我上瘾的是性
But my addiction is to sex.
我的过瘾良药叫莱昂
My drug is called Leon.
有人在吗？
Is there anyone here?
不用理睬她 她不过就是件家具
Ignore her, she's part of the furniture.
婆婆…
Grandma?
瞧
See?
她这儿有毛病 需要效劳吗？
She's out of it. Can I help you?
-我和一位莱昂先生有约  -莱昂？
- I have an appointment with Mr Leon.  - Leon who?
一个法国人
A Frenchman.
哦 那个画光屁股女人的
Yes, the one who draws naked women.
他在房里 二楼九号房
Yes, he's in his room.  Number nine, on the second floor.
那边请
That way.
谢了
Thanks.
这模特是谁？
Who's the model?
伊芳德芙
Yvonne Dove.
好美…
Beautiful...
你肏过她吗？
Did you do it?
还有男模？
And the man?
让你亢奋吗？
Does it turn you on?
你的一切都会让我亢奋
Everything about you does.
好 过来坐我这儿
Please come and sit here.
我们不能这样下去
We can't keep on like this.
我是有夫之妇
I've got a husband.
这就是你不穿内裤的理由？
Is that why you're not wearing any panties?
莱昂…肏我…求你…
Screw me, please...
我的“莫娜”好像火烧火燎
My "mona" feels like it's burning.
莫娜？
mona?
我的“莫娜”
My "mona".
就是这里…这是威尼斯方言
This...in Venetian dialect.
“莫娜” 好美的词语  “莫娜” 真的好美
“mona” beautiful words,  “mona” really beautiful
这个叫“oseo”
And this is the "oseo".
你根本就不想乖乖做个良家妇女
You've no intention of behaving like a good wife.
一天到晚就想被男人肏
You want to get fucked all day long.
你想要个金枪不倒的种马
You want a stallion with a permanent hard-on.
像你一样
Like you.
你一闻到坚挺的鸡巴 就张开双腿…
You open your legs as soon as you smell a hard cock...
进我体内来！
Come inside me!
摸过你屁股的人你都肯给他干！
You say yes to whoever touches your ass!
对…
Yes...
我就是荡妇
I'm a slut.
好口渴
My throat's dry.
我去给你拿点喝的
I'll get you something to drink.
真不错
Wonderfully.
这是特别为你准备的
This is especially prepared for you.
莱昂 谢谢你！
Oh, Leon, thanks!
抬起头来
Head up!
-蒙上眼干嘛？  -因为…
- Why?  - Because.
你想做什么？
What do you want to do?
不会有事的 就照几张相 来！
There'll be alright as some picture, come on!
很好
Good.
太好了 屁股摆一下
Good,  ass put it.
拱起背来
Arch your back.
太棒了
Great.
酷一点 来个酷点的
A little cool, more...
我想拍下你肏屄时候的样子
I'd like to photograph you while you're fucking.
别动
Hold
-是谁？  -来送饮料的
- Who's that?  - He's brought something to drink.
-谁啊？  -别担心
- Who is it?  - Don't worry.
相信我
Trust me.
真解渴啊
I needed that.
他到底是谁？
Who the fuck is it?
-他上不上镜？  -上镜极了 心肝
- Is he photogenic?  - Yes, my dear.
会很喜欢的 等着瞧吧
You'll love it, you'll see.
我全身酸疼
I'm sore all over.
慢慢就好了
It'll wear off soon.
-你就不嫉妒？  -嫉妒谁？那门房？
- Aren't you jealous?  - Who of? The porter?
他不过就是个“振荡器”  帮我们提升激情的辅助品而已
He was just a "vibrator", a sex aid for our passion.
文学节今晚就闭幕了
The festival ends tonight.
我丈夫想要跟我一起参加闭幕晚宴
My husband wants me to go  to the party with him.
可是…我不知道…回到米兰
But... I don't know... it won't be easy to go back to Milan,
回归日常生活
back to everyday life.
这个会有助于你 我的爱
This will help you, mon amour.
呵 莱昂…好美…
It's beautiful.
你真美
You are beautiful.
今晚我要你陪我
You'll spend tonight with me.
-我们开始先来个五万册…  -失陪一下
-We'll buy fifty thousand books first.  -Excuse me.
我们回米兰再讨论吧
We'll discuss it in Milan.
记住啊 圣诞节可是快到了！
Remember, Christmas isn't far off!
-西维娅  -是达里奥
-Silvia.  -It's Dario.
-玛尔塔呢？  -你不知道？
- Where's Marta?  - You should know!
-怎么跑来问我？  -我以为她和你在一起
- You're asking me?  - I thought she was with you.
她关手机了
Her cell phone's off.
或许她是不想和你说话
Maybe she didn't want to talk to you.
-你丈夫呢？  -你问他怎么了？
- What about your husband?  - What about him?
他当然是在巴黎啦
He's in Paris, of course.
我不理解她究竟发生了什么
I don't understand what's happened to her.
亲爱的达里奥 女人要的是被男人占有
Women, my dear Dario, want men to take them,
而不是被理解！
not understand them!
-看见她吗？
-她那浪臀可真惹火
- Seen her?
- She's got a fantastic ass.
打个小小的赌如何？
How about a little bet?
让她见识见识你的本事
Show her what you're made of!
这个大傻屄！
What an asshole!
-大家都在盯着看  -谁还管他们
- Everyone's looking.  - Who gives a damn?
-抛开一切 跟我走吧  -什么行装都不拿？
- Leave everything and come with me.  - Without taking anything?
到巴黎再买就是了
You can shop in Paris.
起码让我回酒店拿几条内裤
At least let me get some panties from the hotel.
你一到丈夫身边就有去无回了
lf you go up to your husband, you won't come back.
我会回来的…
I'll come...
你等着瞧
You just see if I don't.
不 我毫不后悔
No, I don't regret anything.
“你的手在他的肉棒上揉搓 使它硕硬无比”
"Rub your fingers on his stick to make it nice and thick",
我会一边偷窥男生们撒尿一边欢快地哼唱这旋律
I'd sing that rhyme with glee spying on boys as they took a pee.
好多根鸡巴…
So many cocks...
一个糟老头在我回家的路上一路跟着我
A old man dragging his balls followed me all the way home.
“你的小屄长毛没有？” 他含混不清地问
"Is your little pussy furry?" he asked, his speech all slurry.
上床时我担忧 恐惧…
I shook with fear and dread...
浑身颤抖 却在抚摸我的蜜穴
but I stroked my pussy when I went to bed.
你不是第一个肏我屁眼的人
You're not the first one who's stuck it up my ass.
温柔点 会痛 我说道
Be gentle, I said, it hurts.
在这儿射最安全 他说
It's the safest place to come, he said,
然后拼命往里面顶
pushing it all the way in.
当他拔出鸡巴时 上面沾满屎
He pulled it out covered in shit.
我的屁眼在屄眼之前被开了苞
Deflowered in the ass before the pussy.
真是个贱货…
What a slut...
我们都是那样
We're all like that.
我们都有自己的价值
We've all got our values.
这只是时间 地点和大小的问题
A matter of time, place and size.
一个周日的清晨 我和一个医生…
With a doctor one Sunday morning
在诊所还没开门的时候
when the clinic was closed.
他要我把它含进嘴里
He wanted me to put it in my mouth.
那话儿好大 我觉得我都吞不进去
It was so big I didn't think I'd be able to.
还有在海滩暗房和一个摄影师
With a photographer in his booth at the beach,
打着看照片的借口
with the excuse of looking at photos.
他是有妇之夫 但手指相当灵巧
He was married, but very talented with his finger.
在音乐会的楼上包厢和一位同学
With a schoolmate in the upper-tier-box at a concert.
他略显笨拙 但舌功相当好
A bit clumsy, but good with his tongue.
他不仅吻我的嘴 还亲脖子 乳头
Not just in my mouth, but on my neck, on my tits,
亲我的屁股中间和阴户
between my ass cheeks and in my pussy.
婚后六个月 我又勾搭上个陌生人
Married six months and I'm taking it up the ass from a stranger.
假如我不回米兰 他们会怎么说我？
What would they say if I don't go back to Milan?
假如我和这样一个画裸体女人的男人私奔到巴黎？
If I run off to Paris with a man who draws nude women?
你晓得他那一天到晚提醒着 “先生 记住你和这个那个有约”
You know that four-eyed slut who works as his secretary.
的四眼婊子秘书
"Remember the appointment with so and so, sir."
还有那些想出书的骚货
Whores who want to be published,
巴不得爬到桌下帮他吹箫 就像此处这些女人
eager to suck him off under the desk, like these women here
谁都在假装震惊 可是谁不想占据我的位置
who pretend to be shocked but who would all like to be in my place.
达里奥会不在意我
Dario would treat me like an accessory.
可是如果他现在见到我 或许会改变主意
If he could see me now, maybe he'd change his mind.
他的鸡巴就会硬起来
He'd get a hard-on
因为他知道我的蜜穴里有根鸡巴 屁股上有只手
knowing I have a cock in my pussy and a hand on my ass.
西维娅说得没错 嫉妒真是剂生猛的春药
Silvia's right, jealousy is an aphrodisiac.
莱昂是个聪明的美男子
Leon must be as intelligent as he is hung,
但我们的关系又能维持多久？
but how long could our relationship last?
十厘升吧 鸡巴平均能喷射到你体内的量
Ten centilitres, the average amount a cock can spurt on you.
那就是爱所能遗下的仅有一切
That's all that's left of love.
文学节结束了
The festival has ended,
宴会也结束了
the party's over too.
你是在找这个吧？
Is this what you're looking for?
我问你问题呢 回答我！
I asked you a question, answer me!
-我在找我的睡衣  -忽悠精 你知道睡衣就在这儿
- I was looking for my nightgown.  - Liar, you know it's here.
-还真在这儿呢  -知道现在几点了吗？
- Oh, of course it is.  - Know what time it is?
不知道 大概两点吧？
No. Around two?
现在是凌晨五点 你他妈的去哪儿了？
It's five in the morning. Where the fuck where you?
我去哪儿？我陪西维娅出去跳舞了
Where was I? Out dancing with Silvia.
西维娅在宴会上 你怎么谎话不断？
Silvia was at the party, why do you keep on lying?
要是你读过 自然就会明白原因！
If you read it, you know why!
我当然看过
Sure, I read it.
还真是本纪实杰作啊！
It's a real masterpiece!
应该将它出版 在下次文学节时隆重推出
It should be published and launched at the next festival.
里面真是事无巨细滴水不漏
You don't leave anything out.
在你那虚伪的端庄外表下 你却是最放荡的婊子！
Behind that fake veneer of modesty you're the biggest whore of all!
让我来肏你 婊子 你是不是就想要这个？
Let me fuck you, bitch. Is this what you want?
不…
No...
不…达里奥…不要！
No...Dario...no!
你要的！你要我就给你“我的爱”！
Oh, yes! I'll give you the "Monamour"!
你喜欢吗 骚货？说你是我的臭婊子！
Do you like it, slut? Tell me you're my filthy whore!
喜欢 达里奥 我就是你的骚货！你的臭婊子！
Yes, Dario, I'm your slut! I'm your filthy whore!
说你喜欢被我从屁股后面干的时候还含着根鸡巴！
Say you'd like someone in your mouth while I come up your ass!
干吧 我喜欢！
Fuck, yes!
大声尖叫 我的爱！
Scream, Monamour!
那是你承诺给我的结婚礼物！
It's the wedding present you promised me!
西尔维亚是对的 多亏了莱昂 我又重新找回了达里奥
Silvia was right, thanks to Leon I found Dario again.
看过我的日记后 他甚至行为都有点像莱昂
After reading my diary he even behaved like him.
嫉妒真的重新点燃了他的激情？
Did jealousy really rekindle his passion?
那点一直纠缠他的疑心 让他大展雄风
Always having that little suspicion, that's what turns him on.
当他疲倦而又满足之后 入睡前
Before he fell asleep, worn out and satisfied,
他把手放在我的屁股上低声地明知故问：
he put his hand on my ass and whispered knowingly:
你何时再去跟西尔维亚跳舞？
"When are you going dancing with Silvia again?"
哇 多漂亮的车啊
Wow, how beautiful car
你要去巴黎 是吗？
You'll going to Paris, isn't it?
正好搭顺风车 弗朗索瓦 你回酒店收拾好行李 顺便买单
Just get a ride, François, go to the hotel, bags-packing and paying.
-=影片结束 谢谢欣赏=-